excelsior.edu 2015-12-31

# Excelsior College | Privacy Notice

## Privacy

###  **Introduction**

This policy applies to personal information that Excelsior College collects when you use our website or engage in electronic communications with us.

###  **Personal Information Collected by Excelsior**

When you access our website you may voluntarily give personal information to us so we can provide you with requested information or services. Some examples are: your name, address, phone number, and email address. You can always opt not to provide such information to us. However we may not be able to communicate with you.

In addition, during your interaction with our website certain information about your usage of the site is collected automatically, such as: top viewed and visited pages and links on our web site, top entry and exit points, number of form completions, time spent on pages, top downloads, top keywords used offsite to lead customers to our website, your internet protocol (IP) address, information collected via cookies (see below), device event information such as system activity, crashes, hardware settings, browser type, etc.

What are cookies? Cookies are alpha numeric identifiers we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your internet browser to recognize you as a return user of our site. The information we collect is used to make our website and services we provide more customized and beneficial to you.

You may set your internet browser to block all cookies including ours. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will direct you on how to enable or disable cookies. However, some online services will not work if cookies are disabled.

Your continued use of our website is your consent to the collection of this data for the purposes outlined above.

###  **How Excelsior Uses the Information it Collects**

Excelsior uses the information we collect to enhance our web site and the services we provide to you. Excelsior does not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information to third parties for their promotional purposes. Excelsior does share limited information with companies that perform work on our behalf. These companies are required to keep this information confidential and to use it strictly for authorized businesses purposes in accordance with Excelsior College policies.

Excelsior may release personal information when we believe in good faith that it is necessary for us to comply with the law or for the safety of our employees, our customers or others.

Excelsior also shares aggregate information for regulatory or governmental reporting purposes.

###  **Email Communications from Excelsior**

Excelsior often uses email communications to update you about new programs or services that may be of interest to you. Each such email communication contains instructions on how to opt- out of receiving future communications.  Excelsior may receive a confirmation when you open or interact with an email from us if your system permits. We use this information to ensure that future communications with you are as helpful and useful as possible.

###  **Updating Your Information**

If you believe that any information Excelsior has collected about you is inaccurate or which you would like removed from our system, you may be able to change it yourself using the [MyProfile](https://my.excelsior.edu/secapps/go/myprofile) (login required) application. You can also use MyProfile to opt-out of electronic mail communications. Otherwise, please contact the [Office of Registration and Records](http://www.excelsior.edu/about/registration-and-records).

Excelsior uses tools from Google (including Remarketing and Google Analytics Demographics and Interests reports) to track aggregate data on the use of our website. Excelsior and others (including Google) use cookies to inform, optimize, and show you ads most relevant to your interests based on your past visits to our website. Third-party vendors (including Google) may show you Excelsior ads on sites you visit across the Internet. Visit [Google Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) to manage these ad-related services.

###  **Data Security**

Excelsior uses information technology industry best practices to ensure that all personal data is kept secure from unauthorized access.

###  **Use of Social Media**

When customers are accessing Excelsior's staff, students, alumni or content via social media such as Face book, Twitter, etc. users should be aware that they are subject to the terms of use of these services. Customers should read and fully understand the privacy policies and terms of use of these services before accessing them.

###  **Links to Third Party Content or Websites**

The College bears no responsibility for the accuracy of third party or user generated content posted on its website and the opinions expressed by third parties and/or users are not necessarily those of the College or its employees. If the College receives a complaint regarding third party or user generated content on its website the College will follow the procedures required by the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.

When you are on our site you may link to other websites and other websites may contain links to the College's site. These other websites are not under Excelsior's control and such links do not necessarily constitute an endorsement of those sites or the services offered by them. Excelsior is not responsible for the privacy policy, security practices, or content of such third party web sites.

###  **Conditions of Use**

The use of our website is conditioned upon adherence to our terms of use and privacy policy. Any disputes about this privacy policy shall be governed by New York State law.

###  **Amendment of Excelsior's Privacy Policy**

Excelsior reserves the right to amend this policy at any time without notice.

Any questions about this policy should be directed to: [webmaster@excelsior.edu](mailto:webmaster@excelsior.edu?subject=Privacy%20policy%20question)

## Use of Information and Material

The information and material contained on this site, and the terms, conditions, and descriptions that appear, are subject to change at any time without notice. Any information or material on this site may be downloaded for review provided that the user does so for his or her individual, non-commercial use. Such information or material may not be otherwise copied, edited, linked with, or used, in any other Web site, visual, print, or broadcast medium, without the express permission of the College. The College bears no responsibility for the accuracy of Third Party or User Generated Content posted on this site and the opinions expressed by third parties and/or users are not necessarily those of the College or its employees. If the College receives a complaint regarding Third Party or User Generated Content on this site the College will follow the procedures required by the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.
